Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; 7; 1296
  - UAlbany Alumni, 2011 December 20-2016 June 13; 7.4; 78
    - Media and Marketing: 11/19/03 @ 11 AM Downtown Campus Brian Cechniki digital, 2003 December 1; 78.5 MB 79
    - Media and Marketing: 1/13/04 @ 2 PM State Capital, Albany NY Stanley Fink Internship: Donna Bellino digital, 2004 January 27; 106.1 MB 45
    - Media and Marketing: 1/13/04 @ 2 PM State Capital, Albany NY Stanley Fink Internship: Donna Bellino digital, 2004 January 27; 106.1 MB 45
    - President's Office: 1/13/04 @ 5 PM President's House outdoor holiday decoration digital, 2004 January 28; 37.5 MB 25
    - President's Office: 1/13/04 @ 5 PM President's House outdoor holiday decoration digital, 2004 January 28; 37.5 MB 25
    - President's Office: 1/13/04 @ 5 PM President's House outdoor holiday decoration digital, 2004 January 28; 11.4 MB 18
    - Media and Marketing: 9/4/04 @ 11 AM Dewey/Hawly Library Downtown Campus Christa Nymen and Dave Friedfel digital, 2004 September 16; 57.1 MB 48
    - Media and Marketing: 8/23/05 @ 3 PM football field / PE Gym Paul Schwartz digital, 2005 September 6; 89.9 MB 58
    - Media and Marketing: 9/14/05 @ 3:30 PM MSC (side entrance) Great Beginnings Winners: Greg and Debbie Rickes digital, 2005 September 27; 19.6 MB 11
    - Advancement: 10/27/05 @ 10 AM Main Library portrait: Mr. and Mrs. Panton digital, 2005 November 14; 18.9 MB 14
    - President: 11/1/05 @ 11 AM Phi Delta Rm./ Alumni House Benevolent Assoc. Mtg digital, 2005 November 15; 17.7 MB 12
    - Advancement: 5/30/06 @ 9:30 AM Heritage Village Apts. / Guilderland portrait: Joseph Persico, 2006 June 13; 223.9 MB 139
    - Development: 6/13/06 @ 3 PM Alumni House portrait: Jeff Luks and Brian Fessler, 2006 June 28; 464.0 MB 209
    - Alumni Association: 2/3/07 @ 5:30 - 8 p.m. for photography of Big Purple Growl & Ferocious Feast - start out at the Feast at 5:30 p.m. in the University Gym and then take a few shots at the men's game at 7:30 p.m. in SEFCU Arena, 2007 February 1; 168.1 MB 270
    - Alumni Association: Photo Session; various locations for Alumni Weekend_07; email to follow with specific locations and times, 2007 April 24; 612.4 MB 274
    - Alumni Association: Photo Session; various locations for Alumni Weekend_07; email to follow with specific locations and times, 2007 April 24; 612.4 MB 274
    - Alumni Association: Photo Session; various locations for Alumni Weekend_07; email to follow with specific locations and times, 2007 April 24; 383.2 MB 473
    - Alumni House: Photo session; 6/20/07 1844 Society Donor Reception 6 - 8 p.m. @ Life Sciences Bldg., 2007 July 3; 108.1 MB 177
    - MBA Students, 2008 August 27; 464.3 MB 164
    - Kim Corker, 2009 May 6; 20.7 MB 43
    - Tina Hansen, 2009 May 12; 35.6 MB 53
    - Gregory Nowell, 2010 September 21; 50.1 MB 94
- StudentLife, 2005 November 2-2016 June 18; 8; 3043
  - StudentLife, 2005 November 2-2016 June 18; 8.1; 3043
    - Undergrad Admissions: 2/5/02 @ 12:30 PAC stairway group tour leaders digital, 2002 February 15; 21.4 MB 15
    - Media and Marketing: 9/7/02 @ 1 PM Truck Farm - East Berne UAlbany students harvesting corn for Regional Food Bank digital, 2002 September 23; 43.5 MB 67
    - photo session: 11/4/03 @ 1:30 PM Education Bdlg. Lobby various situations for web and print, 2003 November 5; 128.1 MB 93
    - Students in Lecture Center, 2003 December 15; 98.4 MB 44
    - Undergraduate Admissions: Photo Session: 4/27/04 - 4/29/04 Various times and locations View Book Photos; "Day in the Life" of Ashley DeNeal digital, 2004 May 11; 65.2 MB 58
    - Undergraduate Admissions: Photo Session: 4/27/04 - 4/29/04 Various times and locations View Book Photos; "Day in the Life" of Ashley DeNeal digital, 2004 May 11; 65.2 MB 58
    - Business: 5/4/04 @ Noon BA-233 MBA Presentations / group shot (Sanjay Goel's class) digital, 2004 May 13; 10.6 MB 8
    - President: 4/28/04 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom President Ryan's Speech to Faculty digital, 2004 May 13; 55.2 MB 53
    - Media and Marketing: 11/17/04 @ 1:15 PM University Advancement/Media and Marketing UAB Work Study Students digital, 2004 November 24; 33.2 MB 20
    - Media and Marketing: 2/21/05 @ 3 PM studio web feature w/ newspapers and students digital, 2005 May 5; 337.3 MB 184
    - Admissions: 4/26/05 - 4/28/05 various times and locations David Rozen digital, 2005 May 24; 148.0 MB 108
    - Admissions: 4/26/05 - 4/28/05 various times and locations David Rozen digital, 2005 May 24; 148.0 MB 108
    - Fountain Day, 2006 April 24; 540.4 MB 243
    - President: 4/20/06 @ 3 PM - 4:30 PM Standish Room Wendell Lorang retirement party, 2006 April 28; 144.2 MB 75
    - President: 4/21/06 @ 2 PM - 3:30 PM CC Assembly Hall Distinguished Professor Lecture / Edna Acosta-Belen, 2006 April 28; 31.3 MB 15
    - President: 4/28/06 @ 4:30 PM - 7 PM Pres Res / Palace Theater Reception for Immaculee Lilibagiza / Rwanda genocide survivor, 2006 April 28; 789.6 MB 174
    - President: 5/2/06 @ 9 AM - 11 AM various locations / main campus Campus Clean-up Day 2006, 2006 April 28; 166.5 MB 73
    - President: 4/23/06 @ 11 AM Collins Circle Fountain Day 2006, 2006 April 28; 465.2 MB 231
    - President: 4/18/06 @ 2:45 PM Azalea Garden Environmental Task Force / President Hall, Andrei Lapenis, George Robinson and Kathryn Lowery, 2006 May 1; 71.6 MB 32
    - President: 4/27/06 @ 2 PM City Hall Rotunda / Albany, NY Mayor Jennings fetes UAlbany Basketball Team, 2006 May 2; 212.5 MB 100
    - Media and Marketing: 8/15/06 half day Campus Safety Poster images, 2006 August 29; 205.0 MB 144
    - Business: 9/25/06 @ 11:30 AM LC-22 / Outside if nice day group photo: 1st Freshman Class / MIT Program, 2006 August 31; 49.6 MB 24
    - Media and Marketing: 9/7/06 @ 10 AM Parking Management students in line w/ games, 2006 September 21; 30.6 MB 19
    - Advancement: 9/7/06 @ 2 PM CC Fountain students: Dominique Lopez and Iona Armour / UAlbany Magazine, 2006 September 21; 79.8 MB 46
    - Student Success: 10/5/06 @ 9:15 AM PAC for photography of Albany High School and Harriet Gibbons, 2006 October 5; 182.5 MB 87
    - Media and Marketing: 9/27/06 @ 11 AM Science Library Information Commons / room shot w/ close ups, 2006 October 10; 64.1 MB 31
    - Counseling Center: 10/12/06 @ 9 - 11 am at 33 North Lake (between Washington and Western) for Social Norms campaign, 2006 October 12; 660.4 MB 288
    - Development: 10/27 @ 3 PM Front of the Campus Center, 2006 October 27; 60.1 MB 31
    - Development:; 11/10/06 @ 2:00 PM Location: Indian Quad: Honors College students with Jeff Haugaard, 2006 November 7; 250.7 MB 105
    - Media & Marketing: 11/10/06 @ 12 - 1 PM Indian Quad for photo of Professor David Strait and Food for Thought program, 2006 November 10; 50.2 MB 21
    - Development: 11/16/06 @ 11 AM Cancer Research Center at the East Campus for portraits of scientist and other shots., 2006 November 16; 226.8 MB 114
    - Student Success: 11/20/06 @ 10 AM 1 Park Place, 4th Floor, Albany, NY (on Wolf Road, behind Chili's) for photo of David Schultz of Media Logic. Photo session: 11/21/-6 @ 1:45 PM Bank of American building on 69 State Street, Albany for photo of Jennifer McPhee Photo session: 11/20/06 @ 1:30 PM 700 Patroon Creek Blvd for photo of Michael Castellano - SEFCU Check in with admin at front desk, 2006 November 20; 479.4 MB 191
    - University Counseling Center: 2/9/07 @ 1 - 5 pm Science Library by Minerva for photographs for our model's program grant., 2007 February 10; 205.4 MB 340
    - University Counseling Center: 2/9/07 @ 1 - 5 pm Science Library by Minerva for photographs for our model's program grant., 2007 February 10; 205.4 MB 340
    - University Counseling Center: 2/9/07 @ 1 - 5 pm Science Library by Minerva for photographs for our model's program grant., 2007 February 10; 205.4 MB 340
    - Media & Marketing: 3/8/07 @ 4 PM Campus Center Lobby for photo of students for Relay for Life Campus Update story., 2007 March 7; 36.3 MB 53
    - Media & Marketing: 3/29/07 @ 2 PM Campus Center Ballroom for Elizabeth Kolbert seminar., 2007 March 30; 39.3 MB 78
    - Media & Marketing: 4/22/07 @ 11 - 4 PM Podium for Fountain Day event, 2007 May 4; 2.3 GB 394
    - Development: 5/15/07 @ 11:30 AM Indian Quad dining hall for photo of Tina Badi for UAlbany Magazine., 2007 May 15; 20.7 MB 20
    - Advisory Committee on Campus Security: - Act Smart Safety poster needed using a male model., 2007 September 14; 216.0 MB 101
    - Media & Marketing: web feature photo to be taken on 9/12/07 @ 10:20 a.m. in the New Science Library room, SLOG03 with Prof. Asal and student Ben Spear., 2007 September 21; 21.8 MB 69
    - Media & Marketing: 9/11/07 @ 3 p.m. at Melville Hall in the study lounge of the basement, photo of Allyson Impollomeni for update story., 2007 September 25; 29.9 MB 58
    - Media & Marketing: Albany High on 10/1/07 at 4 pm to take shots of ceremony with Eva Joseph, James Anderson, as well as students from both schools, 2007 October 15; 280.1 MB 82
    - Media & Marketing: 11/30/07 from 12 - 4 p.m. to take shots for "Jail or Bail" program taking place in the Campus Center Ballroom for the Disablilty Resource Center., 2007 October 25; 5.4 MB 6
    - Media and Marketing: 11/5/07 @ 12 noon News and Notes students: (1) Emanuel Rivera-Sunjurjo, Roy Offewall and Genki Kudo (2) Megan O'Donnell, 2007 November 20; 56.9 MB 33
    - Rockefeller College: Photo session: Friday Nov. 30, 9:00a.m location: in front of the capitol or another state building downtown, 2007 December 12; 523.6 MB 366
    - Rockefeller College: Photo session: Friday Nov. 30, 9:00a.m location: in front of the capitol or another state building downtown, 2007 December 12; 523.6 MB 366
    - Rockefeller College: Photo session: Friday Nov. 30, 9:00a.m location: in front of the capitol or another state building downtown, 2007 December 12; 523.6 MB 366
    - Media and Marketing: 11/29/07 @ 11 AM clock tower turnaround Hydrogen Fuel Cell Demo Car, 2007 December 13; 18.9 MB 27
    - Media and Marketing: 2/4/08 @ 12:30 pm CC / radio station photo of DJ, 2008 February 18; 145.1 MB 161
    - Media and Marketing: 3/3/08 @ 9:30 AM Sculpture Studio students pouring bronze, 2008 March 14; 172.1 MB 275
    - Media and Marketing: 3/3/08 @ 9:30 AM Sculpture Studio students pouring bronze, 2008 March 14; 172.1 MB 275
    - Epay Campaign Poster, 2008 June 20; 77.0 MB 148
    - Orientation_08, 2008 July 2; 100.6 MB 239
    - Emily Tashjian and Carol Lawlor, 2008 July 7; 38.1 MB 93
    - Orientation_08, 2008 July 8; 100.6 MB 239
    - International Students, 2008 September 10; 120.4 MB 172
    - Empire Crosswalk, 2008 September 11; 21.3 MB 44
    - NY Alert_cell phone, 2008 September 16; 246.7 MB 89
    - students for sustainability, 2008 September 19; 13.1 MB 31
    - carillon room, 2008 October 10; 22.9 MB 59
    - Mackenzie Univ_students, 2008 October 14; 19.5 MB 47
    - signature ice cream, 2008 November 14; 9.6 MB 29
    - Jason Middlebrook, 2009 January 28; 40.5 MB 55
    - BPG_09, 2009 February 8; 334.1 MB 334
    - Boys and Girls Club, 2009 February 28; 50.9 MB 115
    - Alpha Phi Alpha, 2009 March 12; 8.8 MB 60
    - Katerine Pais_Kristen Swaney_Advisement, 2009 May 20; 71.1 MB 49
    - orientation2009, 2009 July 10; 839.0 MB 808
    - orientation2009, 2009 July 10; 839.0 MB 808
    - orientation2009, 2009 July 21; 839.0 MB 808
    - Indian Quad Dining Hall, 2009 August 25; 14.2 MB 19
    - gallery, 2009 August 27; 422.7 MB 216
    - Sherman Memorial Bridge and Placque, 2009 September 2; 91.2 MB 34
    - Deena Yousif_Rachel Galgan, 2009 October 14; 67.6 MB 41
    - Parsons Family and Child Center, 2009 December 12; 62.6 MB 94
    - student census takers, 2010 February 22; 26.6 MB 68
    - students_various locations, 2010 March 23; 236.8 MB 522
    - students_various locations, 2010 March 23; 17.9 MB 23
    - Talbot, Brenda, 2010 June 16; 66.5 MB 90
    - Orientation2010, 2010 July 12; 286.8 MB 551
    - Orientation2010, 2010 July 12; 286.8 MB 551
    - Orientation2010, 2010 July 22; 286.8 MB 551
    - Diversity and Affirmative Action Training, 2010 August 24; 39.3 MB 86
    - Vox Pop, 2010 September 22; 100.4 MB 69
  - Residential Life, 2012 August 23-2016 January 23; 8.2; 646
    - Residential Life, 2012 August 23-2016 January 23; 8.2.1; 646
      - Media and Marketing: 5/9/02 @ 3 PM Empire Commons mock room digital, 2002 May 24; 25.7 MB 21
      - Media and Marketing: 7/17/02 @ 2:15 State Quad Admissions Suite "before shots of room" digital, 2002 July 30; 8.3 MB 24
      - Admissions: 8/22/05 @ 11 AM Indian Quad / Tuscarora 106 interior room shots digital, 2005 September 5; 26.6 MB 16
      - President: 8/26/05 @ 4:30 - 5:30 PM Podium Move in Day Family Picnic digital, 2005 September 5; 127.5 MB 79
      - Media and Marketing: 2/16/06 @ 11 am Empire Commons group shot / three students: Justin Smith, Karla Jaime and Jennifer Alvarez, 2006 February 24; 65.2 MB 27
      - Media and Marketing: 9/2/06 @ 10:30 AM State Quad "Moving In Day", 2006 September 12; 67.4 MB 112
      - ResLife Awards Ceremony, 2009 January 21; 24.2 MB 52
      - Move in 2010, 2010 August 26; 180.2 MB 197
    - Dorms, 2014 April 29-2014 December 19; 8.2.2; 206
  - Student Groups, 2012 December 15-2015 December 14; 8.3; 28
    - University Relations: 2/21/01 @ 11:15 AM CC 165 B Graduate Student Organization Board Meeting digital, 2001 March 6; 146.3 MB 57
    - University Relations: 3/20/01 @ 10 AM CC 375 Latina Alliance digital, 2001 April 3; 15.6 MB 13
    - University Relations: 4/5/01 @ 9 AM CC 375 Russian Olympiad digital, 2001 April 17; 28.6 MB 22
    - Middle Earth: 3/19/02 @ 12:30 PM Health Ctr. - 2nd Fl. Delores Cimini w/students digital, 2002 April 2; 14.4 MB 9
    - Media and Marketing: 11/26/02 @ 9:30 AM CC 314? Radio Station portrait: Tasha Lewis digital, 2002 December 9; 14.6 MB 14
    - Media and Marketing: 4/21/04 @ 12:30 PM Sculpture Garden "Spread the Word" Poetry Slam Team digital, 2004 May 4; 43.1 MB 21
    - Media and Marketing: 4/21/04 @ 12:30 PM Sculpture Garden "Spread the Word" Poetry Slam Team digital, 2004 May 4; 43.1 MB 21
    - Media and Marketing: 5/6/04 @ 10:30 SUNY Tunes Earth Tones digital, 2004 May 20; 72.7 MB 48
    - Media and Marketing: 5/6/04 @ 10:30 SUNY Tunes Earth Tones digital, 2004 May 20; 72.7 MB 48
    - Media and Marketing: 5/21/04 @ 1 PM CC Grad Student Assoc. Rm 165_B Florencia Cornet digital, 2004 June 3; 25.7 MB 16
    - Media and Marketing: 5/21/04 @ 1 PM CC Grad Student Assoc. Rm 165_B Florencia Cornet digital, 2004 June 3; 25.7 MB 16
    - Media and Marketing: 7/8/04 @ 2 PM location TBA Middle Earth Peer Assistance Program / check presentation; Dominion Foundation digital, 2004 July 6; 58.3 MB 37
    - Media and Marketing: 12/13/04 @ 3 PM Middle Earth students: Aliya Makki and J.R. Bethea w/ Delores Chimini digital, 2004 December 23; 37.5 MB 26
    - Media and Marketing: 2/18/05 @ 2:30 PM PE Bldg. Lobby Midnight Basketball League digital, 2005 March 2; 29.8 MB 19
    - Media and Marketing: 2/16/05 @ 3:30 PM A&S 121 President Hall meeting with A&S Dean and faculty digital, 2005 March 2; 16.7 MB 11
    - Media and Marketing: 2/22/05 @ 11 AM PAC lobby Mark Dalton and Kim Engle digital, 2005 March 3; 263.8 MB 98
    - Media and Marketing: 3/30/05 @ 11 AM Middle Earth student counselors digital, 2005 April 13; 124.9 MB 80
    - Media and Marketing: 4/19/05 @ 4 PM CC 375 Voice of the Student: Lori Riley (WGY) with students/faculty members digital, 2005 April 25; 62.6 MB 39
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; 15.8 MB 10
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; 15.8 MB 10
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; 15.8 MB 10
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; 15.8 MB 10
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3:45 PM CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa group photo digital or film?, 2005 May 11; 15.8 MB 10
    - Media and Marketing: 4/26/05 @ 4 PM CC 375 Voice of the Student digital, 2005 May 12; 37.9 MB 28
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; 423.9 MB 267
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; 423.9 MB 267
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; 423.9 MB 267
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; 423.9 MB 267
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Collins Circle Roads Scholar Tour digital, 2005 May 13; 423.9 MB 267
    - Media and Marketing: 5/4/05 @ 11:15 AM CC Fireside Lounge Phi Beta Kappa Faculty Representatives digital, 2005 May 18; 15.5 MB 11
    - Media and Marketing: 5/5/05 @ 1:45 PM CC Assembly Hall BFFA / Alianza reception digital, 2005 May 19; 74.5 MB 41
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; 58.9 MB 32
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; 49.6 MB 34
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; 58.9 MB 32
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; 49.6 MB 34
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; 58.9 MB 32
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; 49.6 MB 34
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; 58.9 MB 32
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ 3 PM University Library / 1 st floor reading and book signing w_KLH digital, 2005 May 24; 49.6 MB 34
    - Media and Marketing: 5/13/05 @ CC Assembly Hall Phi Beta Kappa ceremony / KLH speaking to inductees and parents digital, 2005 May 24; 58.9 MB 32
    - President: 11/16/05 @ 3 PM Alumni House Middle Earth Anniversary Reception digital, 2005 December 1; 458.4 MB 57
    - Media and Marketing: 11/18/05 @ 9 AM CC Patroon Lounge / Cafeteria Student Advocate Group digital, 2005 December 2; 518.3 MB 98
    - President: 12/6/05 @ 1 PM Pres Office Interfraternity Council Meeting w/ Ryan Shaw, Michael Jaromin and James Anderson digital, 2005 December 2; 51.0 MB 14
    - President: 12/8/05 @ 12:00 Noon Alumni House League of Women Voters Luncheon, 2005 December 5; 66.6 MB 31
    - Media and Marketing: 8/3/06 @ 2 PM Univ. Hall group shot for bookmark project, 2006 August 16; 121.7 MB 50
    - Media & Marketing: 10/24/07 @ 1:30 p.m. to take a shot in studio for homepage on Asian Occasion. Donna will bring model here., 2007 November 7; 92.5 MB 161
    - Sichuan Six, 2008 August 21; 10.7 MB 16
    - Organized C.H.A.O.S, 2008 October 16; 17.0 MB 34
    - Third World Impact Student Group, 2009 March 13; 16.5 MB 50
    - Cube Car, 2009 April 16; 93.9 MB 43
    - Sleep Out for the Homeless, 2009 April 22; 22.6 MB 14
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 2009 May 15; 39.0 MB 13
    - Phi Beta Omega, 2009 September 10; 23.6 MB 29
    - SPH_Group, 2010 January 6; 5.7 MB 17
    - SPH_Group, 2010 January 6; 127.0 MB 256
    - SPH_Group, 2010 January 6; 35.0 MB 87
    - bioethics debate team, 2010 February 23; 16.8 MB 21
    - Dutch meet with President Philip, 2010 March 1; 24.3 MB 67
  - Summer Opportunties, 2011 June 26-2015 August 19; 8.4; 312
  - Traditions, 2013 August 22-2016 June 18; 8.5; 528
    - Candelighting Ceremony_Move In Day_2008, 2008 August 23; 75.3 MB 136
  - Year In Review, 2012 August 9-2013 October 28; 8.6; 63